(Sheldon:)to meet other women.
(Penny:)Oh, please, you're
barely interested
(Penny:)in a physical relationship
with one person.
(Penny:)Why would you want to confuse
and disappoint others?
(Sheldon:)Being with Amy has awoken
the sexual creature within.
(Sheldon:)When I see a pretty gal walking
down the street, I think,
"hubba hubba"
like any other guy.
(Penny:)You kiss your mother
with that mouth?
'Cause it's fine.
(Raj:)Here you go.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Raj:)Shall we toast?
(Stuart:)To Howard and Bernadette,
(Stuart:)and the house key they
never asked me to return.
(Bernadette:)You said you got it back.
(Howard:)Well, clearly, I lied.
(Raj:)So how's your apartment?
(Stuart:)Not great. The
electricity's out.
(Raj:)So why don't you get it fixed?
(Stuart:)I called, and they're
like, "Pay your bill!"
Of you ever need somewhere to
crash, there's always my place.